propccleaner.com 2019-01-10

# Pro PC Cleaner Privacy Policy

This privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) discloses how Rainmakers Software, LLC uses the personal information it gathers on this site. We will notify you of changes by posting the new policy on this website.

By using our services or submitting information, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. Your assent to these practices is essential for us to provide our services. You can opt-out and decide not to provide the requested personal information. However, by doing so, we will be unable to contact you. You can also request that we not use any information you provided by emailing [customerservice@propccleaner.com](mailto:customerservice@propccleaner.com).

The personal information we collect includes your name and email address. Our primary use of your personal information is to respond to an inquiry you sent us through our website.

We automatically collect certain information from visitors to our site, such as Internet addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, and clickstream data. We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers. This information is logged to help diagnose technical problems, and to administer our site so that we can constantly improve the quality of the services we provide. We do not respond to your browser’s “do not track” signals or other mechanisms for indicating your preference regarding the collection personally identifiable information.

Our website uses Google Analytics. A complete description of the information that is collected and used, as well as instructions on how to opt-out, are available at www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. We take measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of your information. We carefully limit access to the database in which your personal information is stored. Additionally, we share and transfer your personal information only in the ways set forth in this privacy policy.

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.

This website is directed at teenagers and adults and not to children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly distribute such information. We do not knowingly allow children under the age of 13 to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information through our website. Similarly, because we do not collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, we do not condition the participation of a child under 13 in activities on providing personally identifiable information. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personally identifiable information from someone under the age of 13, we will delete such information from our records. If we change our practices in the future, we will obtain prior, verifiable parental consent before collecting any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

Contact us at the address below if you want us to change or delete any information that we have about you. We will respond to your request to access, update, or delete your information within ten (10) business days. Before we are able to provide you with any information, correct any inaccuracies, or delete any information, however, we may ask you to verify your identity.

This website is owned and operated by:

Rainmaker Software, LLC

1925 Lovering Ave.

Wilmington, DE 19806

Privacy Policy02.02.2015
